

ANGEL ALDRETE

Software Developer

PROFILE

Hey there! I'm Angel, a passionate software developer with 5+ years of experience in DevOps, Mobile, and Web development, with a strong focus on the latter.

I love solving complex problems and being a supportive team member. Let's work together to create something amazing!

SKILLS

HTML, CSS & JS

JQuery

PHP (Codelgniter, Laravel)

React, Angular, Vue

Wordpress, Magento

Docker, Jenkins, Kubernetes

Azure, AWS

ASP.NET

Pythor

Swift - Objective-c, Java, Flutter, Ionic

MySQL

Prometheus, Grafana

Go

CONTACT

Facebook: Angel Aldrete Phone: +52 (686) 112 16 82

Email: angel.aldrete96@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Infosys

2022 - Now

The project and role I have on this company is to develop and maintain solutions for an e-commerce platform that handles transactions, form validations, metrics and data visualizations.

Engrane Digital S. de R. L. de C. V.

2022 - 2022

The project and main role I had in this company was to develop and maintain an insurance car company / e-commerce / appointment app within the constraints of our clients.

CustomSoftwareSolutionz

2022 - 2022

My primary role at this company was developing and maintaining a telecomm application that managed phone data for multiple clients. It was an exciting project that challenged me to innovate and create solutions that met our clients' needs.

Collins Aerospace

2019 - 2022

At this company, I had the opportunity to work on various exciting projects. As a full-stack developer, I developed an internal application for micro services in the Aerospace sector. Later, I joined the Mobile team, where we developed and maintained apps used in airplanes. Finally, I worked on a data management app for airplane metrics.

Catarsis Multimedia

2018 - 2019

As a freelancer in this company, I worked on multiple projects for clients, including blog and e-commerce development and maintenance of static and dynamic sites. I ensured each project was delivered on time and to the client's satisfaction.

TERMINAL

EDUCATION

BACHELOR DEGREE OF DIGITAL GRAPHICAL DESIGNER ENGINEER

CETYS UNIVERSIDAD | 2015 - 2019

WEBSITE

https://angelaldrete.github.io/adamina/

INTERESTS

Music Production - Game Development - 3D Modeling - Woodworking Construction - Cooking